Overriding: out_dir = C:\Users\amitc\OneDrive\Desktop\Research\NanoGpt\nanoGPT\experiments\exp003_embedding96
Overriding: device = cpu
number of parameters: 0.45M
Loading meta from data\shakespeare_char\meta.pkl...


KISTHABRD RII:
And have but shallan he blote of love that thy will
As my prichce shall with all proctes
The be these purtive hear that marwath hat thee
the more sirol the coment hee that sin fore!

CALILLIUS:
Away, will is mun ponce?

MENENIUM:
I lieth wise fare for love I ast me sippeel;
Good but your pam, there that thou aftiest
lave hat as thein as the take and the now thonk.
The man his grow protited to murt for thims he
As sheent be dook cinplouses hat and steend enong shal:
And the he sha
---------------

Made that morrand crannes?
No the dise fale thy my arme.

SICICK:

INot your in the purse that in batter loovio:
I fiepsty thou eyel and a the have a and
And yet the lifef love: fath I let she not.

ORUCENCENIO:
Hak, deadin not mee, that make agel hear! I my ape?

Shest borde I shall defwel-deat them well,
What not.

SPROLO:
You this is mall neace don no! I Inum frast ongod,
And you offore sof of fire pricenth.

BOUKENTE:
Strught the for dovers iffor bun ut than,
And me Ife cone fearce gown thir
---------------

EORCK:
Forst The weat mon you to the not nows he prinen,
Who neaw chappry geast the did the lave have for
Than the geed stoubl slast be the in I therne,
Fo'll devent that in a flivess, whow houngrause chime in.

There, insance prices, ustrence evefer's now,
Be stromany, thou hanse may plase nor hour buc.

ASUCILILANII:
Way, how dought do had master'm bre saught.
For Donether him: no stameds of the dipakes, thing.

KICHARD KII?

STHARD ICHARK:
Wanke will of king the that I bart; the he proan's
Of
---------------

As and briner arfored.  Hond, thest and that a there.

CARGIANIUS:
Well pose the have love as regets it, here your,
Yought was deand age arman idlet brother
By your bond, lenfe not Duch my the lond.

ROMOUCO:
Py I
Do havince the sut murs that the heres.

BELIZA:
That hat I'll prance palies: the well fast rifed,
We I ben be thy word ageft
And my then with weas, my cape at but in the king.

FaNGUS:
INought's murd shak mopar, bore come that welles,
O abin here thim hoft catisused call of rede
To no
---------------


WASERY:
If, you are estement the what dighte a faral.

CICALARENE:
ARYAM:
Peilat O, of faird dinget malf the to sle
What sfore his deave of than the we is to me
God nengeer god dod to the goor fark to he feents of brie;
Whos man supon pett of me your myseelr
Where the a the a shouck that he do't like for
Is warmpoines ship; pilegh and wor nor mamed,
Who is denepess thince warrat your your have thouse;
That have me and bast the died she menting,
There frecerelo the where his our kin owalt.

GROL
---------------

GARDI:
Would they day now, now! I thee the his lese,
And lord yim quone but toge hand, have I ulack,
And wond think boody mele. I spileng, and cown.

RUCININIIB:
He gelest the as me me the un astrer diplence
Seachiud ther's slove should the the mathe.

PAUCENIUS:
Whill I bloque there, in by verwionks.

HPROF OLOLARS:
When prother, londs, then wen I pichaiin.

PELIO:
Hand kernow will will thesing, more'd wich,
Which this fleweran the mast hown cation,
And me to not not my limintity quicken is owi
---------------


There prose swes and so this to and to be thee: you.

MANGLUS:
I carond a grove to me fearfer and parthel
If such martice as sonby's will comse parckil
What is say lidgntes yever too stary will the come
To men for this priju hig laad, the but and weart,
My hape mad thy sall we mough we do keand.

BELIUS:
And nor not the me no sline bore nat ut sirn-deach
Be mathe to hand the him a honer? The leet.
Where, therein that and suke, the trowh.

DUS:
Is; mak and the ut this my it kive will sut me the 
---------------


Thour wille preaveing how reid that gaint be a batce fouf amin
His and haved hodm ifn my by such crounes!

POMKS RICESTERBRDARD:
Ouch, all not it an what shan the for well thend,
And hand in shand, mare and gead male beal,
Twat elat the as of inferes, the pature,
What as as offoand and to that manke li'd thand we,
cat she cont you now hat the and me bet wee
Whou thick of midnes or worown'd underon,
Thoune newer mare love.
The mountaben of that mast they should him.
Who he loodnse be that hounce
---------------

Or this tand that this have he herstres,
No the seart wordes lidan to the son no uslore and.

RAMELUS:
StrowaRII:
And; in aby now'd your love: is wome of the mase
To canseld cown, you sway what rights
Man the and encons. My the spreetes to the hou
Morcious helje torfances, he moren,
I by farmse a know hours porefetly eneat;
As you sleandd to potherDuiang net Cleant.

IKING ICHARD ANGHANT:
Far I im che freel brasher here that it as on pant freent!
I be maners.
GORLENTIETBRD:
I mear forme and to w
---------------

Rup anond ritlorne:
Prompe come liviceses, that brets in know,
Then this word his many markain, this, I mall of se the
him call tirmitly, maning I my sencrise,
To stome and master coppent it to the dates if kine
There fookge have geanter you me didn is lowar,
Shat pan will no pown so the to mady;
My nise fithie courserixe her sevatecke are thum:
Whis thingimet a is mingenot marde,
Whill me it to proor in in our gaatnor
Have grae to well and, priXathivend low,
There that gord peard revitere, wor 
---------------
