Overriding: out_dir = C:\Users\amitc\OneDrive\Desktop\Tutorial Folder\experiments\exp002_embedding64
Overriding: device = cpu
number of parameters: 0.20M
Loading meta from data\shakespeare_char\meta.pkl...


VIN RIXE:
ICil in lake it depanie would. But Virders,
Were hare fret of warthow by hen for in furet?

CONRTULUS:
ELathy youre thixp wore as us then yourse,
This ip hape beay anden Chist fors our nodst
buth's tho and sist the heralss the hat shechy lourstl.

BERDSIO:
Whe, not your und boty resiancery lagh, Clizes
I veake loward hy sover stagend ale; do hear to hill for.

HENGLOOUS:
And, hou;
Alld nown deaghtiren, four whard swith, will My gaive,-
I nat it the this lare, shavar than haus mang
Bui
---------------

I and of thre and the the tand a ist timpte;
Thous thy thim hand coref thoule mavet,
To the thous more say for hert vearren, lays
Whand thas here no, the sour int me,
I in didsts hit my sovent, for hans jartnoun sand fear.

LEORCE:
And I than ut anrk it ligher shave.

This the core shen It the were,
And in shaply'd his imbled are wich must a mate
to them menupactas withers, sour nof sort to
but bole ants conig nee sict knoods,
Les sout the dencearss our farvivengso'
And a of hey avel thur dike a
---------------

All me this wills undriong homed sid! Paved hein,
He shand thoulde and conen the trences tung,
I a ferike a sthand ond now the seld bete.

HENCHESTY TOPTHORD:
I soull why a yous prortht my nouth duge a hord,
And havll our the trowe of wetry this shisse amAns
O pirtherer the arre this this hus lave; shis noust
Mredent an tront the uld batthan lomed on wto
Thinke, what we domp the ould nee have,
Whe I't and is the ans aver of best to ally mant
Sorat now he this the my wee, we necorn a Geare;
O'd t
---------------


Sto gookes; heres tis hent, truged the my shak the can my and
As twhould of and o'd sith ot and the ole.

SGLUCIO:
Bhat beccine ane chat on mucker we the nouges,
And my somsere, o you the to treceang of the
Tenpotith oncesil, she in hell blod,
Lead in the hat me nan aber an the ay treess
To be the acand to ible ispitings, Ipen his theds
As afff precctix-knanf the ustend your in san the
Tor lopthn thim prown hir, me unde butht
Herer seros for o
Tar han best the linting lurs. Muces we bed
And not
---------------

Matteer done noth tould heren; sover angaio;
Whe kis the oof wold love veangh arks,
Ar a shen prema to mine leche herd, with shis
I mald not a thaw we 'is ris gent, urworre wree sthe
As af rike amoris,
In beation, stake buth deoverd ach anef so hand
And to o lay tall ley adang, the call?

AU'K:
My will is you soune tear mose lood con pye
Oull ast inonteres of lave che ourse the the
Thou my pay for sour nobrent he at rin thee me with,
What han lay hise of lavesfor or susent fil
And the oldy how, 
---------------

GLEOUSSARE:
I min my ushe kis mand the ourens wown and recour,
And suy tre cormong his me whe hich housht have
would gussen as grost harres sure muces,
I of rame in of sicchelo sealiw ur
For thwils all shand cont sean.

AEKINCBP: I share is nother, hast but morke.


GUCECETIXERES:
By his oud hen seay your flad, sear man ving,
And thimss enot elourer in for's bust.

HERG HORY MARVs IORE:
And that he cine on bust hat'd ands he ore avie,
And thou that by pore for lighe, remert andid
That thy mall d
---------------

G ARIO:
Whelo, preat'lond lies,
Be the the would onter renent, melt,
I dirst shing lifeir and thath butt hersuce.
I Shat thighs goster umong knoor thins of ubrced lats?

GUMIAT:
No you that is theely, sike your homst.

OLUMESS:
Shand you as thou the loe not told am stoule the not;
Est ing youl plorned and you in doves to conoung.

COROLIA:
O'l frad, not thy tere in now other, nomourse hat hom
The hit oplen apemy peanr yow; she pret gromss
I efre us had twak whe the thou dadiod,
I drat licteng br
---------------

Ply mord are, that a venle we hit my me you fefor
But lecen mon ofor to this fave, he shouding,
And and the sother isencere of laathtr with ine
Of gaiks af chas these brark tis dendem: the sloe?
And best efor shis wather berch tis of liend;
Wath'd my dour he souch hif ast, deact you
And upllon the and sprut, he oFour of with tagh camas the thanck
Os downel sey thou samed, nobe feth dotiches'n
Thee thy to lagh, fores ba hape she the's ourte
In praysturer in asper pasicte
To thad bee eno bight wic
---------------


ICARD unowely for bocht have lante, anding and thou
Your I cham housh'd sheme dure the inght fore,
Whe thous fapte that cos umblely net earr tis
the to weide sher to arr'st the sorre sale,
O, murram mas fust it the pind it
grest trown os a a fered wars, weand then ma's cony
For the thy and mainges this sorther
Reseiustis bepomeens house, thou I,
Shis salr ho, the abch this as the firt betir.

LINCIO:
O, the bere we is paklen and pandry. Wing hank slow!
I bo sengad are dectors thush this it that
---------------

ESd sto dexasore the beirt and a that,
As gaing tho creave the trempteren hous
swerely me youlde mors mamon ands hand if;
Souck of that werm and ith hedow loverk in thad
In all quenear, the dave reiiveg siven;
That and his me to wore sulf cunikes.

GLIXINNCKA:
We mun sarough lidses, 'plak, and his, hat the as.
I Foulls 'parsian the to your have dought
Bun your mad hope sut the chees that soulo;
Saciand to there im me for sintt stranes.

Fhom; oxe with to feart be list thempan' there?

DUCHORTHAR
---------------
