Overriding: out_dir = C:\Users\amitc\OneDrive\Desktop\Research\NanoGpt\nanoGPT\experiments\exp004_embedding112
Overriding: device = cpu
number of parameters: 0.61M
Loading meta from data\shakespeare_char\meta.pkl...

So dight the thould is him onne of thou we your enming,
The henge
That you our of hims his this hath branther
Theing to peint, mather and in faster.
Some not bister it will anl la's,
He soon I beful did stides percous the unter
Seanre, you prance to mie; the are mither,
That my sprovan hunat my wilt the we this dakes;
And me eye wake my bragast the bell.

:
ANorn:
Airkep, I is a lay? 't be the Lest.
.

ThOMENA:
Then see do.
Hadloog a that stant for melch are in
Is a us mayy lord; it aut the of b
---------------

I criopenting lordy my kill.

DEDW:
Grose for lething the mee brow I and my tow
Thon more the offest coure a the: I thy once,
Ef have unse it hie, prod thee a hee; in and theoul
I a peart part their bith, and of Have them.

YORCHIA:
I well the thop that father, give of dom to game,
Anding will at and I grack for a cricht.

Withinker: you was be his spearion, the hip acy.

MENINIUS:
I have the you wend mell othek the that to supe
And is a be net to be they parst to the game hady.

CABUTELLO:
Noav
---------------

CARIZANULIO:
No me preive siself.

CLANUS:
But have sisrelur of our this lowner!

ACAMILA:
I the day lendce theing of,
Copeny to that manter have weth grettly whrire,
A word herer the hap-do burt wom you siffer.

CISANIULCEO:
I fice, it is to me prove proct, in that may him;
But ut to fall brother, boon more tret he fear gath
The ten will ofsen aglownd to the cound heir,
Thou so, twen thought won to shat
Mauchter in thate my hours;
What that will it us well fromon she terne
To cate mercaline to 
---------------

nave there. And gay, consed:
Tat sway speor, extre sto demer come a bost!
Do I hent your your fastle un seal to morning.
Padiourses is my pleation, him
In gamace- your and taint we owar our shat trugher
Rique treser for Goodse the to sour fould.

SARINCIO:
I pay thou copperias baur in a bear a ward,
Maratins thou plans of or and folded faint.
See thank is noo master trow hath faing me trone
Thou lother be stay.

ABELLIO:
Wherw tAs me to mell of doudge up thy geath:
For grive twilt in surt him?


---------------


BUCUS APELIO:
Ay, no might: weat switle me no we my dade
The will or in amportiamenture.

DORITES:
Tho caster abling so have nogle.

CAMINGWAS:
And to wich dissely to ware puon a
Thenured your fermainpess the beers,
He deast I well thy heat of a brother pervee
Of Contitiver: swak, is the live cust,
More gat diger, thou having as is on aturle?

DUmersting I an woon the ouse badome there.

DUCIO:
I of worman you, ere he let partion,
Be forend I et mites dend. ur to deands wity the that
The this t
---------------

with could be And do ripose veing in of hould:
Breanting my frear this of' I kine ee.

ORWARDIO:
Be that the be of Led
Aup the will a perencers uppy of I linggh,
On that live this that wath art that to hand
She is by the ton the and mother eye,
To in a the lather. Hen a it is of sould a cand-he wee
For sto distarte, his by faace; the do stay.

DUKE VINCENTIO:
Wen!

TBENESTIUS:
Whell mastere I was light a heard the's God
If his to in thenoule vathering outh sherk forth'd whosed a mears,
And the h
---------------

Surde not thy may now
that the wortorther fales. Tirght his this reand;
Then twick:' my to meading hat be hert;
And framest of halge dee spleak that ton to seain my
Shere their with poon kines for heare.

MENCUS:
Thou lelves may that the a
Richoun to a sanil.

CAULIA, that the cout the made.

HAFRI
MINABULA:
Ay, 'Tuch's slame mare thee feer desberfore.

CARIYARZAN:
Thou shave I,
In not do fruncelt of I queat ware my stree to eEd
Sie thange: I I thour pastince a and will abe reather
And that stor
---------------


KING ERG MEORKE:
Not, Is oll it my be, you and sinel the at forther
To we hear befath cusen him shite than furd:
I look in his hand, I not him, and theart,
The will ear to plaince uss thrathed streed.

KING RICHAR you haten asdentaty I rewerlant,
So the a his to then thew to aloat fand of there
All hencer wore in the dother own,
And goonal of pation. I net son rest fromeds,
Or this on spear as 'fure for Yourk in then which damber.

VITELKED:
The sword to for may cellye's the ternce, here
And ac
---------------

MENE:
Ar Bewardiet forter; and dot shall to dighther,
bear was that this your on tearthy the on wee deash
Whom will tike on have monine, now the from to deart,
Goter cam caling in it
Non to will of the ales?

Feire's a pay sinderfourt there,
So won in nole notues him, you gie suchours;
As beict thou hous he mupble brest on beer
Botheres with marpper's us too frome he chalful:
'The so heave of sir,
In thy you and do broner is it eis
There will of the the prenceriet your he somfes
As call Ernd it 
---------------

HORK:
Auld be a do of your gatwers un their hered,
Or comeroughtener this nother in the as toous his
His lowatios him ituar boood and minent,
Withe nother the wife fathy, we the trothey wore
Thick you reck ant it of hathersel ut,
But furt dreabher of willam oul now, the thou me:
'Time our that selling, where onself,
And Is undue tand to he thim thine's fart
That frombure in upins a upesour teend.

BORTESTER:
I thee Well I mort this be tookes,
The sall heeffor jeest and were be preesiuty.
And hat
---------------
