Overriding: out_dir = C:\Users\amitc\OneDrive\Desktop\Tutorial Folder\experiments\exp001_baseline
Overriding: device = cpu
number of parameters: 0.80M
Loading meta from data\shakespeare_char\meta.pkl...

I by done what leave death,
And aproposely beef the are and sors blate though wat our fort
Thine the aftior than whating bods farse dowed
And nears and thou stand murs's consel.

MEOF:
Sir, should and then thee.

GRICHARD one, enceling:
Or house
Your to do the all in despery I parve porge,
And shall not aple bralance the my plife friend.
Why should not seed liSian be me,
A light strought weart a king here shall
And so arttion I breatio:
Trale time him the witHer's bout thing thy a moy
A to therr
---------------

To furd of sonce on it my lord my prove.

ICIRIIA:
He had and I clann what would sy pile.

MYUKE MIOF OYCE:
Shall
Pule are wen way bane and thought I a the thems
Thet me staing and ous the broted a well.

MUDINE:
Have was he sir, tye as tor thee o, the beod
And I sto be in to do bun a go.

BORWARDch:
That a heaven my cournamants, wo that art is way.

QUEEN CARWIUS:
For dight erge masters: lold the had in but sway faulter
thing miring conserly.
Why thouf than souch low the kings, bot here,
'I tha
---------------

To lack evice in spray.

PORIOLEN:
Come?

JULIET:
You ! it dother?

That lo, that sur, Securtion; as and I that in
A call in a world intree hous parcious thought the
less lordy this high stater own for of dight;
But twith she have shoul pray wave to to spice here such;
The be the to done do infelf anate.

JULIET:
If you speak:
Thoug you heart my outh be.

BUTHOK:
I powel, tor you leath a it thought helf;
And not take waul us like! Would I have never?
There and fuar souring stay frear in clifest,
---------------

Thire trech theirssing fily with good a be Romate
stanted I all swand you garely faten!
Thy onse lidy for hibe.

SISABELLA:
If we it deay is word wherepak.

LLEO:
But deeds murige have you should you shoulds detle,
So would he are recuren forth heir of,
Of this that fair my kending, my be reave shee.
That have heer dedy sing the the couse bease.

MERDIEL:
I heard be ladick in death in the my weard,
I should the are good you that one bothan were
To good dight, should is mouse enem your Claiin
Tha
---------------

To the is rarne that fath persising with's not of his me?
The love you love word the him him,
As hat worth the lest the a harter presart and lord;
Bet lordow Rick, and muwil I neave warn theirs in death,
And more his think shalt coors you huse say.

VELDO:
As I wail of you a day all bepence the pard,
Bust that a love king a gace man,
As in my later sood I coursues my the time.
ISA ward I dus we thouse the condeling him man.

KING YLOK:
Fy doou have king a which warty the of the our
Lades, this b
---------------

I were they to dower thy lought sur,
Fer hight mother us on toth, the not a more
Forcal the server the preat and heaver where as he
and a a with hast my the hibst the wril not
Whoo the undring to poon a the sore, wough the are
The be and so proond lought proung and and our bouness
On off the thou, the sir but the takes?

Whild be fort them: pourt, therefolt: shall stay I
As you mall should and there to faid's here the teverd:
What he pristing with to thight take no their!

ARCENIO:
We me the hav
---------------

That of the Emand remporrant tell dlep sheed
Met murder him his repustred bid but punnaroughter.

LUCIO:
The sie, art what a carse so forgelied3 this the kning,
Thue in he are amewaring of that fort you Wast in create,
That beet he's shanged ward the exty
But seand shand and Nupe abuly, I wartice so vee
The counsed word mophe hold own so inde the under:
He should my grief pouns the lade this I know,
All me, are would couses to with me ere's sone;
Off a infeared with in the when we repories,
That
---------------

And yeat shall which hath good deefing arm gull that the heave fach
That the made this be low mard,
That his all he be me oun toought pardunges not
A Commoned heir by the whom is proud,
I sill and and for in she were the had.

CARIO:
Should and perven hy herser named.
What I will me shall I do hopse net of your cout
Hat hus face the worse popes the lie
The done brow hous infeer in manes him not:
Which with should in dies you:
With Varrent your not you wardand,
And he not han worging dight nor th
---------------

MENIO:
I would it gear; and my hands wome
Thin, he hadse as may beed the beatt be that of
My sorder agant nempone him be I sujuse ofse
That sway be rest, no he proppur and be of shall go
Onge, onry house hemon the course,
The is a fiend to shall Levoule quores'd onsel
That I comed a my kid not angead of treant
the fail the of coursier groam'dly
The a look him the provereds you him the Prase.

COLUS:
Vord:
Then sir, not whom ame lest there pastarm'd doge and
That here had for peast. I sain, the t
---------------

Romest and the facll by lords him,
Not that lop, thou are frien when,
Which nought ye fair safy same, wrow you,
what not the do con the sunry coursel
The ill hims urn this one arme our too?

LADO:
You beand our king upor teept more put thein;
You do mile spord of unfent all of death lied,
As a that he beck his not with tie my ret our
Than with the wommer not lonks consomes'd?

MORCUSE:
That you have bod love mort are sead the how.

KING RIC& Eymewing:
Away hat baine whem ske fall be thee leath,

---------------
